const qa =[
    {
        question: "How can I donate to mosque restoration projects?",
        answer: "You can donate by clicking on the 'Donate' button on our website. Choose your desired donation amount and follow the secure payment process to make your contribution."
    },
    {
        question: "Can I choose which mosque to support with my donation?",
        answer: "Absolutely! You have the option to select a specific mosque restoration project from our list of ongoing initiatives."
    },
    {
        question: "Is my online payment secure?",
        answer: "Yes, we take the security of your payment seriously. Our website uses encryption and secure payment gateways to protect your personal and financial information."
    },
    {
        question: "What is the minimum donation amount?",
        answer: "There is no minimum donation amount. Every contribution, no matter how small, makes a meaningful impact on our restoration projects."
    },
    {
        question: "How do I receive updates on the progress of the mosque restoration projects?",
        answer: "We will provide regular updates via email newsletters, our website's news section, and social media platforms. You'll be informed of milestones achieved and the impact of your donations."
    },
    {
        question: "Can I make a recurring donation?",
        answer: "Yes, you can choose to make a one-time donation or set up a recurring donation to support our ongoing efforts."
    },
    {
        question: "Can I donate in honor or memory of someone?",
        answer: "Yes, you can make a donation in honor or memory of a loved one. Let us know, and we can provide a special acknowledgment for your thoughtful gesture."
    },
    {
        question: "How do you select the mosques in need of restoration?",
        answer: "We work closely with local communities and religious leaders to identify mosques in need of restoration. Our selection process ensures the greatest impact for the community."
    },
    {
        question: "Can I volunteer to assist with restoration efforts?",
        answer: "Yes, we welcome volunteers who are passionate about our mission. Reach out to us, and we'll provide more information on how you can get involved."
    },
    {
        question: "Are there any specific projects or initiatives associated with the mosques?",
        answer: "Yes, we have various restoration projects, including structural repairs and interior refurbishment initiatives associated with the mosques we support."
    },
    {
        question: "How are the funds allocated for mosque restoration projects?",
        answer: "Donations are allocated based on the specific needs of each mosque restoration project, ensuring that funds are used efficiently and transparently."
    },
]

export {qa}